Finding Aid for the William W. Berry, Jr. Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Mark G. G. Barry Collection
1895-1928
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0554
.11 linear_feet
Biography/History
William W. Berry, Jr., attended Vanderbilt University, receiving a Bachelor of Arts Degree in 1968, and a Doctor of Laws in 1972. The photographs were donated in 1990.
Scope and Content Note
This collection contains 22 items comprised of 11 photograph copy prints and 11 negatives documenting the Beta Theta Pi Fraternity, Beta Lambda Chapter, at Vanderbilt University. The formal portraits are arranged by year, in 11 folders, with only some members identified.
- Photographs – by year
  - 1895
  - 1906-07
  - 1907-08
  - 1910-11
  - 1911-12
  - 1915-16
  - 1923-24
  - 1924-25
  - 1925-26
  - 1926-27
  - 1927-28